<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<root>
<0>
<type>Not an Error</type>
<name>OK</name>
<description>Your account has been successfully added. 0 indicates a success.</description>
</0>
<401>
<type>Agent Error</type>
<name>NO_CONNECTION</name>
<description>Problem Updating Account(401):We're sorry, your request timed out. Please try again.</description>
</401>
<402>
<type>UAR Error</type>
<name>STATUS_LOGIN_FAILED</name>
<description>Credential Re-Verification Required (402): We could not update your account because your username and/or password were reported to be incorrect.  Please re-verify your username and password.  </description>
</402>
<403>
<type>Agent Error</type>
<name>INTERNAL_ERROR</name>
<description>Problem Updating Account(403):We're sorry, there was a technical problem updating your account. This kind of error is usually resolved in a few days. Please try again later.</description>
</403>
<404>
<type>Agent Error</type>
<name>LOST_REQUEST</name>
<description>Problem Updating Account(404):We're sorry, there was a technical problem updating your account. Please try again later.</description>
</404>
<405>
<type>UAR Error</type>
<name>STATUS_USER_ABORTED_REQUEST</name>
<description>Update Request Canceled(405):Your account was not updated because you canceled the request.</description>
</405>
<406>
<type>UAR Error</type>
<name>STATUS_PASSWORD_EXPIRED</name>
<description> Problem Updating Account (406): We could not update your account because the 
<SITE_NAME> site requires you to perform some additional action. Please visit the site or contact its customer support to resolve this issue. Once done, please update your account credentials in case they are changed else try again.
</description>
</406>
<407>
<type>UAR Error</type>
<name>STATUS_ACCOUNT_LOCKED</name>
<description>Account Locked (407): We could not update your account because it appears your 
<SITE_NAME>  account has been locked. This usually results from too many unsuccessful login attempts in a short period of time. Please visit the site or contact its customer support to resolve this issue.  Once done, please update your account credentials in case they are changed.
</description>
</407>
<408>
<type>Agent Error</type>
<name>DATA_EXPECTED</name>
<description>Account Not Found(408): We're sorry, we couldn't find any accounts for you at the 
<SITE_NAME> site. Please log in at the  
<SITE_NAME>  site and confirm that your account is set up, then try again.
</description>
</408>
<409>
<type>Site Error</type>
<name>STATUS_SITE_UNAVILABLE</name>
<description>Problem Updating Account(409): We could not update your account because the end site is experiencing technical difficulties.</description>
</409>
<411>
<type>Site Error</type>
<name>STATUS_SITE_OUT_OF_BUSINESS</name>
<description>Site No Longer Available (411):The 
<SITE_NAME> site no longer provides online services to its customers.  Please delete this account.
</description>
</411>
<412>
<type>Site Error</type>
<name>STATUS_SITE_APPLICATION_ERROR</name>
<description>Problem Updating Account(412): We could not update your account because the site is experiencing technical difficulties.</description>
</412>
<413>
<type>Agent Error</type>
<name>REQUIRED_FIELD_UNAVAILABLE</name>
<description>Problem Updating Account(413):We're sorry, we couldn't update your account at 
<SITE_NAME> site because of a technical issue. This type of problem is usually resolved in a few days. Please try again later.
</description>
</413>
<414>
<type>UAR Error</type>
<name>STATUS_NO_ACCT_FOUND</name>
<description>Requested Account Type Not Found (414): We could not find your requested account at the 
<Account Name> site. You may have selected a similar site under a different category by accident in which case you should select the correct site.
</description>
</414>
<415>
<type>Site Error</type>
<name>STATUS_SITE_TERMINATED_SESSION</name>
<description>Problem Updating Account(415): We could not update your account because the 
<SITE_NAME> is experiencing technical difficulties.
</description>
</415>
<416>
<type>Site Error</type>
<name>STATUS_SITE_SESSION_ALREADY_ESTABLISHED</name>
<description>Multiple User Logins(416): We attempted to update your account, but another session was already established at the same time.  If you are currently logged on to this account directly, please log off and try after some time</description>
</416>
<417>
<type>UAR Error</type>
<name>STATUS_DATA_MODEL_NO_SUPPORT</name>
<description>Account Type Not Supported(417):The type of account we found is not currently supported.  Please remove this site and add as a  manual account.</description>
</417>
<418>
<type>Site Error</type>
<name>STATUS_HTTP_DNS_ERROR_EXCEPTION</name>
<description>Problem Updating Account(418): We could not update your account because the 
<SITE_NAME> site is experiencing technical difficulties. Please try later.
</description>
</418>
<419>
<type>Agent Error</type>
<name>LOGIN_NOT_COMPLETED</name>
<description>Problem Updating Account(419):We're sorry, we couldn't update your account because of unexpected variations at the 
<SITE_NAME> site. This kind of problem is usually resolved in a few days. Please try again later.
</description>
</419>
<420>
<type>UAR Error</type>
<name>STATUS_SITE_MERGED_ERROR</name>
<description>Credential Re-Verification Required (420):The 
<SITE_NAME> site has merged with another. Please re-verify your credentials at the site and update the same.
</description>
</420>
<421>
<type>UAR Error</type>
<name>STATUS_UNSUPPORTED_LANGUAGE_ERROR</name>
<description>Invalid Language Setting (421): The language setting for your 
<SITE_NAME> account is not English. Please visit the site and change the language setting to English.
</description>
</421>
<422>
<type>UAR Error</type>
<name>STATUS_ACCOUNT_CANCELLED</name>
<description>Account Reported Closed (422): We were unable to update your account information for 
<SITE_NAME> because it appears one or more of your related accounts have been closed.  Please deactivate or delete the relevant account and try again. 
</description>
</422>
<423>
<type>Site Error</type>
<name>STATUS_ACCT_INFO_UNAVAILABLE</name>
<description> No Account Found (423): We were unable to detect an account. Please verify that you account information is available at this time and If the problem persists, please contact customer support at 
<SITE_NAME> for further assistance.
</description>
</423>
<424>
<type>Site Error</type>
<name>STATUS_SITE_DOWN_FOR_MAINTENANCE</name>
<description>Site Down for Maintenance(424):We were unable to update your account as the 
<SITE_NAME> site is temporarily down for maintenance. We apologize for the inconvenience.  This problem is typically resolved in a few hours. Please try later.
</description>
</424>
<425>
<type>Site Error</type>
<name>STATUS_CERTIFICATE_ERROR</name>
<description>Problem Updating Account(425): We could not update your account because the 
<SITE_NAME> site is experiencing technical difficulties. Please try later.
</description>
</425>
<426>
<type>Site Error</type>
<name>STATUS_SITE_BLOCKING</name>
<description>Problem Updating Account(426): We could not update your account for technical reasons. This type of error is usually resolved in a few days. We apologize for the inconvenience.</description>
</426>
<427>
<type>UAR Error</type>
<name>STATUS_SPLASH_PAGE_EXCEPTION</name>
<description>Re-verification Required (427): We could not update your account due to the 
<SITE_NAME> site requiring you to view a new promotion. Please log in to the site and click through to your account overview page to update the account.  We apologize for the inconvenience.
</description>
</427>
<428>
<type>UAR Error</type>
<name>STATUS_TERMS_AND_CONDITIONS_EXEPTION</name>
<description>Re-verification Required (428): We could not update your account due to the 
<SITE_NAME> site requiring you to accept a new Terms & Conditions. Please log in to the site and read and accept the T&C.
</description>
</428>
<429>
<type>UAR Error</type>
<name>STATUS_UPDATE_INFORMATION_EXCEPTION</name>
<description>Re-Verification Required (429): We could not update your account due to the 
<SITE_NAME> site requiring you to verify your personal information. Please log in to the site and update the fields required.
</description>
</429>
<430>
<type>UAR Error</type>
<name>STATUS_SITE_NOT_SUPPORTED</name>
<description>Site No Longer Supported (430):This site is no longer supported for data updates. Please deactivate or delete your account. We apologize for the inconvenience.</description>
</430>
<433>
<type>UAR Error</type>
<name>STATUS_REGISTRATION_PARTIAL_SUCCESS</name>
<description>Registration Requires Attention (433): Auto registration is not complete at 
<SITE_NAME> site. Please complete your registration at the end site. Once completed, please complete adding this account.
</description>
</433>
<434>
<type>UAR Error</type>
<name>STATUS_REGISTRATION_FAILED_ERROR</name>
<description>Registration Requires Attention (434): Your Auto-Registration could not be completed and requires further input from you.  Please re-verify your registration information to complete the process.</description>
</434>
<435>
<type>UAR Error</type>
<name>STATUS_REGISTRATION_INVALID_DATA</name>
<description>Registration Requires Attention (435): Your Auto-Registration could not be completed and requires further input from you.  Please re-verify your registration information to complete the process.</description>
</435>
<436>
<type>UAR Error</type>
<name>REGISTRATION_ACCOUNT_ALREADY _REGISTERED</name>
<description> MFA error:  Account Already Registered (436):Your Auto-Registration could not be completed because the site reports that your account is already registered.  Please log in to the 
<SITE_NAME> to confirm and then complete the site addition process with the correct login information. 
</description>
</436>
<505>
<type>Site Error</type>
<name>STATUS_SITE_CURRENTLY_NOT_SUPPORTED</name>
<description>Site Not Supported (505): We currently does not support the security system used by this site. We apologize for any inconvenience. Check back periodically if this situation has changed. We suggest you to delete this site.</description>
</505>
<506>
<type>UAR Error</type>
<name>NEW_LOGIN_INFO_REQUIRED_FOR_SITE</name>
<description>New Login Information Required(506):We're sorry, to log in to this site, you need to provide additional information. Please update your account and try again.</description>
</506>
<507>
<type>Agent Error</type>
<name>BETA_SITE_WORK_IN_PROGRESS</name>
<description>Problem Updating Account(507):We're sorry, Yodlee has just started providing data updates for this site, and it may take a few days to be successful as we get started. Please try again later.</description>
</507>
<508>
<type>Agent Error</type>
<name>INSTANT_REQUEST_TIMEDOUT</name>
<description>Request Timed Out (508): We are sorry, your request timed out due to technical reasons. Please try again.</description>
</508>
<509>
<type>Agent Error</type>
<name>TOKEN_ID_INVALID</name>
<description> MFA error:  Site Device Information Expired(509): We're sorry, we can't update your account because your token is no longer valid at the 
<SITE_NAME> site. Please update your information and try again, or contact 
<SITE_NAME>'s customer support. 
</description>
</509>
<510>
<type>Site Error</type>
<name>STATUS_PROPERTY_RECORD_NOT_FOUND</name>
<description>Property Record Not Found (510):The 
<SITE_NAME> site is unable to find any property information for your address. Please verify if the property address you have provided is correct. We suggest you to delete this site. 
</description>
</510>
<511>
<type>Site Error</type>
<name>STATUS_HOME_VALUE_NOT_FOUND</name>
<description>Home Value Not Found (511): The 
<SITE_NAME> site is unable to provide home value for your property. We suggest you to delete this site. 
</description>
</511>
<517>
<type>Agent Error</type>
<name>GENERAL_EXCEPTION_WHILE_GATHERING_MFA_DATA</name>
<description>Problem Updating Account (517) :We'resorry, there was a technical problem updating your account. Please try again.</description>
</517>
<518>
<type>UAR Error</type>
<name>NEW_MFA_INFO_REQUIRED_FOR_AGENTS</name>
<description> MFA error:  Authentication Information Unavailable (518):Your account was not updated as the required additional authentication information was unavailable. Please try now. </description>
</518>
<519>
<type>UAR Error</type>
<name>MFA_INFO_NOT_PROVIDED_TO_YODLEE_BY_USER_FOR_AGENTS</name>
<description> MFA error:  Authentication Information Required (519): Your account was not updated as your authentication information like security question and answer was unavailable or incomplete. Please update your account settings. </description>
</519>
<520>
<type>UAR Error</type>
<name>MFA_INFO_MISMATCH_FOR_AGENTS</name>
<description> MFA error:  Authentication Information Incorrect (520):We're sorry, 
<site> indicates that the additional authentication information you provided is incorrect. Please try updating your account again. 
</description>
</520>
<521>
<type>UAR Error</type>
<name>ENROLL_IN_MFA_AT_SITE</name>
<description> MFA error:  Additional Authentication Enrollment Required (521) : Please enroll in the new security authentication system, 
<Account Name> has introduced. Ensure your account settings in 
<Cobrand> are updated with this information. 
</description>
</521>
<522>
<type>UAR Error</type>
<name>MFA_INFO_NOT_PROVIDED_IN_REAL_TIME_BY_USER_VIA_APP</name>
<description> MFA error:  Request Timed Out (522) :Your request has timed out as the required security information was unavailable or was not provided within the expected time. Please try again. </description>
</522>
<523>
<type>UAR Error</type>
<name>INVALID_MFA_INFO_IN_REAL_TIME_BY_USER_VIA_APP</name>
<description> MFA error:  Authentication Information Incorrect (523):We're sorry, the authentication information you  provided is incorrect. Please try again. </description>
</523>
<524>
<type>UAR Error</type>
<name>USER_PROVIDED_REAL_TIME_MFA_DATA_EXPIRED</name>
<description> MFA error:  Authentication Information Expired (524):We're sorry, the authentication information you provided has expired. Please try again. </description>
</524>
<525>
<type>Agent Error</type>
<name>MFA_INFO_NOT_PROVIDED_IN_REAL_TIME_BY_GATHERER</name>
<description> MFA error:  Problem Updating Account (525): We could not update your account for technical reasons. This type of error is usually resolved in a few days. We apologize for the inconvenience. Please try again later.</description>
</525>
<526>
<type>UAR Error</type>
<name>INVALID_MFA_INFO_OR_CREDENTIALS</name>
<description> MFA error:  Credential Re-Verification Required (526): We could not update your account because your username/password or additional security credentials are incorrect. Please try again. </description>
</526>
<801>
<type>Not an Error</type>
<name>REFRESH_NEVER_DONE</name>
<description>Request In Progress: Please wait while we update your account.</description>
</801>
<802>
<type>Not an Error</type>
<name>REFRESH_NEVER_DONE_AFTER_CREDENTIALS_UPDATE</name>
<description>Updating Account (802): We are in the process of updating your account with revised credentials</description>
</802>
</root>